Guide to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Records, 1868-1991 bulk (1981-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio Visual Series, 1963-1990, undated(bulk 1981-1990) (Box 66-68)
  - Audiocassettes Subseries (Box 66-68)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Sponsored Activities, Chronological (Box 66-68)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-25)
      - 1983: Radio Talk Show, KLIK, Jefferson City (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-26)
      - 1984 Mar. 24-25: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-1)
      - 1984 Mar. 24-25: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-2)
      - 1984 Mar. 24-25: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-3)
      - 1984 Mar. 24-25: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-4)
      - 1984 Mar. 24-25: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-5)
      - 1984 May 17: Blue Collar Women Testimony for Federal Highways (2 tapes; 2 copies each) (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-6)
      - 1984 May 17: Blue Collar Women Testimony for Federal Highways (2 tapes; 2 copies each) (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-7)
      - 1984 May 17: Blue Collar Women Testimony for Federal Highways (2 tapes; 2 copies each) (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-8)
      - 1984 May 17: Blue Collar Women Testimony for Federal Highways (2 tapes; 2 copies each) (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 84-9)
      - 1984 June 16: Economics Project (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-10)
      - 1984 June 16: Economics Project (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-11)
      - 1984 June 16: Economics Project (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-12)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-13)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-14)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-15)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-16)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-17)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-18)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-19)
      - 1984 July: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-20)
      - 1984 Oct. 15: Meeting planning press strategy regarding United States Department of Transportation press conference (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-21)
      - 1984 Oct. 15: Press conference regarding Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Complaint to the United States Department of Transportation, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-22)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-23)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 6, Audio-cassette 84-24)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-25)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-26)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-27)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-28)
      - 1984 Oct. 27-28: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-29)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-30)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-31)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-32)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-33)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-34)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-35)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-36)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-37)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-38)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 7, Audio-cassette 84-39)
      - 1984 Dec.: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Conference (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-40)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-41)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-42)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-43)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-44)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-45)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-46)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-47)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-48)
      - [1981-1984]: Interviews with women (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 84-49)
      - 1985 Jan. 27: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Blue Collar Women Discussion (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 85-1)
      - 1985 Mar. 5: Clarence Pendleton, National Press Club Luncheon (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 85-2)
      - 1985 Mar. 17: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Hilton Head, S.C. (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 85-3)
      - 1985 Mar. 23: Women and the Law Conference, Nontraditional Workshop (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 85-4)
      - 1985 Mar. 30: Billie Jean Young: Luncheon speaker (Box 66, Case 8, Audio-cassette 85-5)
      - 1985 Apr. 17-18: Staff Program Planning, Shakertown, Ky. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-6)
      - 1985 Apr. 17-18: Staff Program Planning, Shakertown, Ky. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-7)
      - 1985 Apr. 17-18: Staff Program Planning, Shakertown, Ky. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-8)
      - 1985 Apr. 17-18: Staff Program Planning, Shakertown, Ky. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-9)
      - 1985 Apr. 17-18: Staff Program Planning, Shakertown, Ky. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-10)
      - 1985 Apr.: Conference Planning Committee: Evaluation, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-11)
      - 1985 Apr.: Conference Planning Committee: Evaluation, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-12)
      - 1985 Apr.: Conference Planning Committee: Evaluation, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-13)
      - 1985 Apr.: Conference Planning Committee: Evaluation, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-14)
      - 1985 May 3: Brainstorm (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-15)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-16)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-17)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-18)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-19)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 66, Case 9, Audio-cassette 85-20)
      - 1985 May 3-5: Blue Collar Women Workshop, Dayton, Ohio (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-21)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-22)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-23)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-24)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-25)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-26)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-27)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-28)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-29)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-30)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-31)
      - 1985 Aug. 9-11: Leadership Meeting, Montreat, N.C. (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-32)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-33)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-34)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 10, Audio-cassette 85-35)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-36)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-37)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-38)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-39)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-40)
      - 1985 Aug. 11: Meeting (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-41)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-42)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-43)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-44)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-45)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-46)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-47)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-48)
      - 1985 Oct. 12-13: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Carnahan House, Lexington, Ky. (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-49)
      - 1985: Memorandum, Betty B. Mayo to Dorsey Thomas, Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Complaint: Insufficient Statistical Data in First Six States (Box 67, Case 11, Audio-cassette 85-50)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-1)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-2)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-3)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-4)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-5)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-6)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-7)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-8)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-9)
      - 1986 Mar. 14-16: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, Little Rock, AR (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-10)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-11)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-12)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-13)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-14)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 12, Audio-cassette 86-15)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-16)
      - 1986 Mar. 16-18: Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-17)
      - 1986 June 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-18)
      - 1986 June 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-19)
      - 1986 June 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-20)
      - 1986 June 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-21)
      - 1986 June 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-22)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-23)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-24)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-25)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-26)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-27)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-28)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-29)
      - 1986 Oct. 16-18: Steering Committee Meeting, Marydale (Box 67, Case 13, Audio-cassette 86-30)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-1)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-2)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-3)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-4)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-5)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-6)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-7)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-8)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-9)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-10)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-11)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-12)
      - 1987, Mar. 6-7: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley Hotel (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-13)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-14)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 14, Audio-cassette 87-15)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-16)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-17)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-18)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-19)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-20)
      - 1987, June 1-2: Steering Committee Meeting (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-21)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-22)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-23)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-24)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-25)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-26)
      - 1987, Oct.: Steering Committee Meeting, Highlander (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 87-27)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 88-1)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 88-2)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 15, Audio-cassette 88-3)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-4)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-5)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-6)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-7)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-8)
      - 1988, Mar. 27-28: Meeting, Little Rock, Ark. (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-9)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-10)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-11)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-12)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-13)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-14)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-15)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-16)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-17)
      - 1988, Nov. 5-7: National Conference Planning Committee, Chicago (Box 67, Case 16, Audio-cassette 88-18)
      - 1989, July 10-12: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley House (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 89-1)
      - 1989, July 10-12: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley House (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 89-2)
      - 1989, July 10-12: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley House (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 89-3)
      - 1989, July 10-12: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley House (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 89-4)
      - 1989, July 10-12: Steering Committee Meeting, Harley House (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 89-5)
      - 1990, July 19-22: Steering Committee Meeting, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 90-1)
      - 1990, July 19-22: Steering Committee Meeting, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 90-2)
      - 1990, July 19-22: Steering Committee Meeting, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette 90-3)
      - Answering machine (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-1)
      - Answering machine: In-house staff meeting (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-2)
      - Answering machine messages (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-3)
      - Answering machine: Out of town (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-4)
      - Answering machine: Out of town, variable (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-5)
      - Answering machine: Regular overnight (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-6)
      - Confernce on Black Women (Box 67, Case 17, Audio-cassette ND-7)
      - Dictation tape: Memo to staff: CONFIDENTIAL, RESTRICTED, regarding personnel (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-8)
      - Discussion regarding follow-up of United States Department of Transportation complaint: Work in Ohio (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-9)
      - Fillmore, Mary (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-10)
      - First meeting of four day conference (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-11)
      - Friday: Day two (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-12)
      - Introduction: Union overview (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-13)
      - Interviews, Sevier County, Tenn. (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-14)
      - KAHN Workfare Conference, Feb. 26 (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-15)
      - Meeting (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-16)
      - Meeting (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-17)
      - Meeting (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-18)
      - Meeting (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-19)
      - Meeting: Committee reports (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-20)
      - Planning meeting (Box 67, Case 18, Audio-cassette ND-21)
      - Planning meeting (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-23)
      - Planning meeting (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-24)
      - Planning meeting regarding Women's Opportunity in Road Construction (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-25)
      - Planning session for meeting (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-26)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting, June 9 (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-27)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition phone messages (enigmas) (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette ND-28)
    - Non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Activities, Chronological (Box 68)
      - 1963: Civil Rights Rally, Washington, D.C. (Includes Martin Luther King speech) (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-1)
      - 1979?: Nelly Morton (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-2)
      - 1982: Profile of Marian Write Edelman: The Children's Defense Fund Options in Education Series, National Public Radio (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-3)
      - 1982: Maureen Reagan at the National Press Club, National Public Radio (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-4)
      - 1985, May 5: Homer Lindsay, First Baptist Church, Jacksonville, Fla. (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-5)
      - 1986, Apr. 16: Rural Leadership: Katherine Waller, Rubin Snake, Tom Mosgaller (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-6)
      - 1986, Apr. 15: The Changing American Family: Juana Bordas, Maxine Brown, Andrew Billingsly (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-7)
      - 1986: Power Communication, Career Track, Inc., Lexington, Ky. (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-8)
      - 1986: Power Communication, Career Track, Inc., Lexington, Ky. (Box 68, Case 19, Audio-cassette NS-9)
      - 1986: Power Communication, Career Track, Inc., Lexington, Ky. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-10)
      - 1986: Power Communication, Career Track, Inc., Lexington, Ky. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-11)
      - Si Khan (music) (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-12)
    - Non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Activities, Alphabetical (Box 68)
      - Council on Foundations, 35th Annual Conference, Denver, Colo.: Births and Deaths of Foundations: Attitudes, Economics and Regulations 1984, Apr. (Box 68, Case 20, Audio-cassette NS-13)